<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="lumbinigarden">Lumbini Garden</string>
    <string name="lumbinigardenDesc">Lumbini Gardens is a public park on the banks of the Nagawara Lake in Bangalore, Karnataka, India named after Lumbini of Nepal dedicated to Lord Buddha It contains an eco-friendly boating park and a 12,500 square foot artificial beach and children’s pool</string>
    <string name="wonderla">Wonderla Bangalore</string>
    <string name="wonderlaDesc">Wonderla Holidays Limited is a leading amusement park designing and operating company in India headquartered near Bidadi, 28 kilometres (17 mi) from Bangalore. It is promoted by Kochouseph Chittilappilly and his son Arun Chittilappilly. Wonderla\'s flagship amusement park located at the same address is the second theme park project from the company and has been operational since October 2005. It is spread over an area of 82 acres (33 ha). The first amusement park, Wonderla Kochi, was set up in 2000. The third amusement park project Wonderla Hyderabad was commissioned in April 2016. The parks have been set up with a total investment of over ₹7.5 billion (US$110 million).</string>
    <string name="bangalorefort">Bangalore Fort</string>
    <string name="bangalorefortDesc">Bangalore Fort began in 1537 as a mud fort. The builder was Kempe Gowda I, a vassal of the Vijaynagar Empire and the founder of Bangalore, now Bengaluru. Haider Ali in 1761 replaced the mud fort with a stone fort. The army of the British East India Company, led by Lord Cornwallis on 21 March 1791 captured the fort in the siege of Bangalore during the Third Mysore War (1790–1792). At the time the fort was a stronghold for Tipu Sultan. Today, the fort\'s Delhi gate, on Krishnarajendra Road, and two bastions are the primary remains of the fort. A marble plaque commemorates the spot where the British breached fort\'s wall, leading to its capture. The old fort area also includes Tipu Sultan\'s Summer Palace, and his armoury. The fort has provided the setting for the treasure hunt in the book Riddle of the Seventh Stone.</string>
    <string name="tipusultanpalace">Tipu Sultan\'s Summer Place</string>
    <string name="tipusultanpalaceDesc">Tipu Sultan\'s Summer Palace, in Bangalore, India, is an example of Indo-Islamic architecture and was the summer residence of the Mysorean ruler Tipu Sultan. Hyder Ali commenced its construction within the walls of the Bangalore Fort, and it was completed during the reign of Tipu Sultan in 1791. After Tipu Sultan\'s death in the Fourth Anglo-Mysore War, the British Administration used the palace for its Secretariat before moving to Attara Kacheri in 1868. Today the government of Karnataka maintains the palace, which is located at the center of Old Bangalore near the Kalasipalyam bus stand, as a tourist spot.</string>
    <string name="bangalorepalace">Bangalore Palace</string>
    <string name="bangalorepalaceDesc">Bangalore Palace, a palace located in Bengaluru, Karnataka, India, was built by Rev. J. Garrett, who was the first Principal of the Central High School in Bangalore, now known as Central College. The construction of the palace was started in 1862 and completed in 1944. In 1884, it was bought by the then Maharaja of Mysore Chamarajendra Wadiyar X. Now owned by the Mysore royal family, the palace has recently undergone a renovation.</string>
    <string name="electronicscity">Electronics City</string>
    <string name="electronicscityDesc">Electronics City, usually referred to as Electronic City, is an IT hub in Anekal taluk in the Indian state of Karnataka, India. It is one of India\'s largest electronic industrial parks, spread over 332 acres (1.3 km²) in Konappana Agrahara and Doddathogur villages, inside Bangalore, India. It consists of three zones called phases – Phase I, Phase II and Phase III. Electronics City was established by Keonics, Karnataka Electronics, a pioneer in information technology infrastructure development. Keonics Electronics City houses major IT /ITES companies. There are approximately 200 IT/ITES companies located in Electronics City.</string>
    <string name="kempegowdamuseum">Kempegowda Museum</string>
    <string name="kempegowdamuseumDesc">Kempegowda Museum is a government museum located in the city of Bangalore, in the state of Karnataka, India. It was established in the year 2011 is dedicated to Yelahanka chieftain Kempegowda (1513-1569) who is the founder of Bangalore city. The museum is located on the first floor of Mayo Hall. The museum has Kempegowda\'s statue as well as posters and pictures of forts, temples, reservoirs and inscriptions from his time.</string>
    <string name="HALmuseum">HAL Aerospace Museum</string>
    <string name="HALmuseumDesc">HAL Aerospace Museum is India\'s first aerospace museum located at Hindustan Aeronautics Limited premises, in Bangalore. Established in 2001, the Museum is part of the HAL Heritage Centre and Aero Space Museum, and showcases the growth of the Indian aviation industry and HAL for six decades. The museum houses displays of various aircraft and helicopters, Aircraft engine models, Flight simulators, a mock Air Traffic Control Tower and exhibit of Indian aviation history. The Museum is maintained by HAL (one of Asia\'s largest Aerospace companies).</string>
    <string name="amusementpark">Amusement Parks</string>
    <string name="historicalmonument">Historical Monuments</string>
    <string name="itpark">IT Parks</string>
    <string name="museum">Museums</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
</resources>
